The Swimming Dead
Zombie Shark is a horror, science fiction, tv
movie film directed by Misty Talley.
A perfect getaway weekend turns into a nightmare for four friends who find
themselves fighting for their lives against an experimental shark.
In order to survive they must fight sharks, zombies, and shark zombies.
Amber, played by Cassie Steele.
Maxwell, played by Jason London.
Dr. Palmer, played by Laura Cayouette.
Lester, played by Roger J. Timber.
Jenner, played by Ross Britz.
Sophie, played by Sloane Coe.
Zombi 2 is a 1979 English-language Italian zombie film directed by Lucio Fulci.
It was adapted from an original screenplay by Dardano
Sacchetti to serve as a sequel to George A.
Romero's Dawn of the Dead (1978), which was
released in Italy under the title Zombi.
The film was released as Zombie in the United States and
Zombie Flesh-Eaters in the United Kingdom.
It stars Tisa Farrow, Ian McCulloch, and Richard Johnson, and features
a score by frequent Fulci collaborator Fabio Frizzi.
The film is set on a Caribbean island cursed by voodoo whose dead
residents rise as zombies to attack the living.
A scientist's daughter journeys to the island after her
father's boat turns up abandoned in New York City.
Intended by its writer as a return to "classic zombie tales", Zombi 2 was filmed in
Italy, with further location shooting in New York and Santo Domingo.
Produced on a small budget of 410 million Italian lira, the film earned
several times its production costs back in international gross.
It attracted controversy upon its release in the United
Kingdom, where it became listed as a "video nasty".
However, in the subsequent years the film received a greater
appreciation from critics, and has gained a cult following.
The film explores themes of monster, mad
scientist, zombie animals, zombie, shark.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.